{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":33,
 "infinite":false,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztmk0OwiAUhNl5oF7Qc7ms1+muFzAmkhBCKa8\/zsCbxaxs5Ht8U7TGJYSwKIoh607uWquFATEz2gfS9ZVdOLtWvi6KYSbwNp\/wcLUL6z3c+7qM\/lt78E8no6ZX\/6XrH4o5LP4fG05b3c\/KoaDdpx0onQMW9+gZtmZCc\/TGVetA\/tpEPM\/7FzRHL1zR4yT\/Lrm2\/Nc6IP\/jcMm\/by75983V6j\/tgPyPwyX\/vrnk3zeX\/Pvmann+X4K+\/43KJf++uUr+a+5z\/xPBDDGvEJ5p0DzsXLnH3v1\/eeJ9xnQ2sXJt+bf8\/i\/\/\/XLJv28u+ffNVfOfdkD+x+Q66n8l9Z\/\/zw7Nw86V+i85Tq+tdYA16P2NQe\/DXkpuW54D42cBaxg6EM9I1rS6r3WANSz+0ftwJLWZ0Gzyj3Nv8Y\/ujUf\/d3izvJ9lb67uZU+xznjH3oy+x8r5fACtN2z4",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":128,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztmkEOwjAMBH3jQf0g7+LYL\/EB1EOlyGoTG8fNpt2R9gKo2WYMKgURQnx8G8lay9Ihi6vOF42W656zEF1Lrzuqw+pcM4OtQ2RGe7rwvodnXxfRv3UOrnRy18zq\/+g8trwYV1D877HMwJl7xh8UzmZAU3OPBnv5sMwA\/cdB7+Xxvwj++aCB3mtzWrsOoP8Y6L3oPxf0XvSfC3qvln8R+o+A3ov+c0HvRf+5oPei\/1zQe2n\/Gl7\/xUDvRf+5oPcq\/Wtq9\/+Wa2qa+Ii8y4zus4PaS3uc3T\/xcebfc\/+f\/ueF\/p8N\/T+bmv9yBvTjq9D\/HSj969\/\/Z\/Sv\/2eHAmovq385eG6dICiM3gdLtF\/L98DyMwAxCDOAvj9W9ztHr0UNiv\/R+\/BPaozuRv\/j3EvgOPQ\/1l0v\/7Xjeeg9lzPhPceMvbn7HpM4Pzazpps=",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":128,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":709,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":208
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":710,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":711,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":384,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":712,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":48
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":713,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":688,
                 "y":40
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":714,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":735,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":759,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":761,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":765,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":368,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":768,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":772,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":672,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":774,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":784,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":64,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":785,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":752,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":512,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":753,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":816,
                 "y":16
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":755,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":756,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":757,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":770,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":168
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":787,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tiledversion":"1.1.6",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":198,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":235,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":259,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":287,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":450,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":821,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1126,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1321,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3305,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3531,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3819,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4051,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4115,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/breakable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4425,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5866,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5998,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6073,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6427,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6885,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6890,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6932,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7136,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7358,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7643,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "type":"map",
 "version":1,
 "width":128
}